狮子座，祝贺胜利，祝贺进球。
Leo, congratulations on the victory, congratulations on the goals.
Leo, felicidades por la victoria, felicidades por los goles.
两个月没有踢球了。
Two months without playing football.
Dos meses sin jugar al fútbol.
你感觉如何？
How did you feel?
¿Cómo te sentiste?
你是怎么做到的？
How did you do it?
¿Cómo lo hiciste?
好吧，事实是有点累。
Well, the truth is that a little tired.
Bueno, la verdad que un poco cansado.
该部分...
The part...
La parte...
迈阿密的潮湿和炎热对我们也没有多大帮助。
The humidity and heat of Miami doesn't help us much either.
la humedad y el calor de Miami nos ayuda mucho tampoco.
但是，嘿，我真的很想离开这个领域很长一段时间。
But hey, I really wanted to get back out of the field for a long time.
Pero bueno, tenía muchas ganas de volver mucho tiempo fuera de la cancha.
但好吧，过了一段时间我开始和球队一起训练，我感觉很好并且......
but well, after a while I started training with the group, I felt good and...
pero bueno, de poquito me fui entrenando con el grupo, me fui encontrando bien y...
这就是为什么我们决定开始，我们非常高兴，非常高兴。
and that's why we decided that it was going to start and we were very happy, very happy.
y por eso decidimos que iba de arranque y muy contento, muy feliz.
这个赛季进展顺利，他们已经接近冠军了，尽管还有很长的路要走……他们在更衣室里谈论了多少这些？
The season is going very well, they are close to the title, although there is still a long way to go... how much do they talk about all that in the locker room?
La temporada va muy bien, están cerca ya del título, aunque todavía falta... ¿de qué tanto hablan de todo eso en el vestuario?
不，正如我们一开始所说的，我们知道我们的计划并且......
No, as we said at the beginning, we knew the plan we had and...
No, como dijimos al principio, sabíamos el plan que teníamos y...
这是一个目标，对吧？
And it's a goal, right?
Y es un objetivo, ¿no?
我们是现实的，我们不...
We are realistic and we do not...
Somos realistas y no hacemos...
我们负责。
We take charge.
Nos hacemos cargo.
事实是，这一年我们运气不好，受伤了。
The truth is that during the year we had a lot of bad luck with injuries.
La verdad es que durante el año tuvimos mucha mala suerte con las lesiones.
我们从来都...
We were never...
Nunca estuvimos...
一切总是因为这样或那样的原因而丢失。
Everything was always missing for one reason or another.
Todo al completo por una cosa u otra siempre nos faltaron.
球员和球队始终。
players and the group always.
jugadores y el grupo siempre.
继续吧，今天我们首先要...
went ahead, today we are first with a...
salió adelante, hoy estamos primero con una...
一个很大的差异，当之无愧，我希望我们可以
a big difference and deservedly so and well I hope we can
una gran diferencia y merecidamente y bueno ojalá podamos
完成顶部...
finish on top for...
terminar en lo más alto para...
了解它的含义以及之后发生的事情。
for what it means and for what comes after as well.
por lo que significa y por lo que se viene después también.